<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Hitchhiking | Bodey Baker]]></title>
  <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/categories/hitchhiking/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-10-31T22:39:31+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Bodey Baker]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[bodey.baker@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Day 2 & 3: Getting to Carnarvon and relaxing]]></title>
    <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/2012/07/10/day-2-3-getting-to-carnarvon-and/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-10T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/2012/07/10/day-2-3-getting-to-carnarvon-and</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
<br /><div class="p1"><table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="float: right; margin-left: 1em; text-align: right;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-z4uaKPRMVTQ/T_yuJ5lrY0I/AAAAAAAAEe0/HyV9ZZLgHmY/s1600/IMG050.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="clear: right; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" height="320" src="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-z4uaKPRMVTQ/T_yuJ5lrY0I/AAAAAAAAEe0/HyV9ZZLgHmY/s320/IMG050.jpg" width="240" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">Butter with Kyle's Raphael</td></tr></tbody></table>I'm in Carnarvon and these guys are awesome. I love backpackers. Butter, her boyfriend and their friends are great. Now I just need to work out what to get them as thanks. People that say "nothing" suck&nbsp;<img goomoji="softbank_ne_jp.329" src="https://mail.google.com/mail/u/0/e/softbank_ne_jp.329" style="background-color: white; font-family: arial; font-size: small; margin: 0px 0.2ex; vertical-align: middle;" /></div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1">So, I woke up yesterday morning and wrote out the last post, then did some Korean study, packed my things that had left my bag and started walking down the road with my thumb out. It wasn't too long until someone felt sorry for me and turned their car around to pick me up. Actually, I felt sorry for them. With the amount of sleep I'd had the night before, there was no way I was going to be great company. Luckily, he loved talking so we did fairly well. I convinced him to stop at one of the road houses so that I could have a real brunch unlike the two kiddie sized chocolate bars I'd had for breakfast. Needless to say, I've spent most of today preparing. Making sure all my clothes are clean and packed, buying a cheap sleeping bad and throwing away half the crap that made it's way into my bag. Well… mostly it's just half of my first aid kit and spending the $47 in loose change I was somehow carting around.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1"><table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="float: left; text-align: left;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-tssRFqYmFYE/T_wwZWTq4UI/AAAAAAAAEeo/I9s3_cnT8fA/s1600/IMG049.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="clear: right; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" height="240" src="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-tssRFqYmFYE/T_wwZWTq4UI/AAAAAAAAEeo/I9s3_cnT8fA/s320/IMG049.jpg" width="320" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">I suck at poker</td></tr></tbody></table>I digress, back to the bloke who picked me up. He had a daughter who jumped straight in the back of the car giving me the front seat. I never know how to handle that too well but it's the norm so you just kind of mutter out a thanks. The bloke who picked me up was a Kiwi with a pet hate for the rivalry between the two countries. He educated me on a few points that I haven't bothered to check, like Farlap being from New Zealand and told me a fair bit about Carnarvon. He loved smoking, could no longer drink and had hitch hiked along the west and east coast when he was younger along with having done a bit of squatting. He'd apparently once done it with two guys who murdered someone who picked them up just for the cash in their wallets. Apparently you wouldn't of picked that they were capable of it but they were easily stupid enough to do something that…. stupid. So, after a brief stop at the cemetery, he gave me a tour of the town and dropped me off at my friends house.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1">I've now spent one night here and plan on heading off early tomorrow morning. It's raining now (my jumper was on the line outside) but should be clearing up by the morning. Wait! The rains stopped! I might try and get some stuff done in town before it starts up again!<br /><br />Oh. The plan is to stop in Dampier, Port Hedland, South Hedland, Broome and then... well I'll sort that out then. That is, presuming the plan hasn't changed by then.</div></div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Day 1: A good start]]></title>
    <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/2012/07/09/day-1-good-start/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-09T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/2012/07/09/day-1-good-start</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
<br /><div class="p1"><table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="float: right; text-align: right;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-oRFHH0ij6Pg/Si45Oz00twI/AAAAAAAABFY/TLZVxmIeJWM/s1600/n591195959_303442_195.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" height="320" src="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-oRFHH0ij6Pg/Si45Oz00twI/AAAAAAAABFY/TLZVxmIeJWM/s320/n591195959_303442_195.jpg" width="240" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">Me at the Gravity Center for the Magic 8-Ball trip.</td></tr></tbody></table>Ah! It's good to be moving. I woke up at some ungodly hour to do my tax and pack. Then Esu, Dougy and I drove to T's before heading to my hitching point near Muchea. It took very little time for my first lift to pick me up.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1">He was a guy from south England somewhere and was going to the gravity centre in Gingin. He'd been to most of the tourist sites in Perth and couldn't wait for the two years until his contract was up fast enough. He dropped me in Gingin and we bonded over how things closed too early in Perth and that the living wasn't dense enough. The standard stuff.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1">The next guy was a year younger than me (although he thought I was younger). He had a bunch of tattoos (some of which he'd done), built custom bikes (the reason he'd been in Perth), worked as a DJ, had done some work in security and was now working in the airport. He'd also travelled a surprising amount of Australia. He dropped me at the Geraldton maccas (so cheap) at two pm but said he could drop me off at a backpackers. I'm now on the side of the road somewhere north of there. Grumpy is probably a word that would come to mind. I'm just glad it's not raining.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1">This currently has a startlingly similar feel to the time when I was hitch hiking, maybe in townsville, where three lovely African girls took me to their families house where I helped cook and babysit the children and they fed me. Then they tried to bring me out to a party with them and told me that it was no problem and they'd sort somewhere out for me to crash the night. I said no. I said that a truck driver might pick me up over night and take me a long distance. Sometimes I need to be beaten until I'm unconscious and then when I wake up, beaten again just to drive the point home. That was a stupid decision and this one seems no better.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1"><table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="float: left; margin-right: 1em; text-align: left;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-TaS_a0-NilM/T_wUHw4C0FI/AAAAAAAAEeQ/hzItLdv3bi0/s1600/IMG047.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="clear: left; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" height="240" src="http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-TaS_a0-NilM/T_wUHw4C0FI/AAAAAAAAEeQ/hzItLdv3bi0/s320/IMG047.jpg" width="320" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">If you squint, that's Lee!!</td></tr></tbody></table>Anyway, turning down that lift lead to me meeting Lee. I'd just made it to the outskirts and had a lot of people driving past pointing. It was rather futile though because I hadn't made it to the unknown intersection ahead, so I had no idea which way I'm going. Anyway, Lee was a French hitch hiker who was on my turf and was also heading to Carnarvon that night. He didn't seem to have much luck and nor did I after meeting him. I stopped hitch hiking and walked a few km's past him before sticking my thumb out again. Only to see him drive past in the longed for comfort of the passenger seat of some car. He didn't even wave! And then… a few km's further, we crossed paths again. I hadn't managed to get a lift and apparently his fell quite a bit short. I should probably point out that Lee was doing the wise thing and waiting next to the 24hr service station. I walked past him again and got a phone call from Sammy at around sunset which I stopped short since a car was stopping for me.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1"><table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="float: right; margin-left: 1em; text-align: right;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-HHX-hM4oWSI/T_wV1lvd60I/AAAAAAAAEeY/026-KdxTlGg/s1600/IMG048.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="clear: right; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" height="320" src="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-HHX-hM4oWSI/T_wV1lvd60I/AAAAAAAAEeY/026-KdxTlGg/s320/IMG048.jpg" width="240" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">The family didn't even see it!</td></tr></tbody></table>My next lift was a family that took me into Northampton. The girl, who was around my age, was telling me about how she'd briefly owed monkeys in Indonesia. They also explained that Northampton's population of 1000 was enough to support three bars. Upper, middle and Lower. Or was it First, Second and Third? Meh. They were amazingly creative names. I had a beer in the last one. I was hoping for some food but the kitchen was closed. The girl behind the bar was a gorgeous Italian girl. We talked a bit about travelling and then instead of:</div><br /><ul><li>asking about accommodation,</li><li>hitting on her, or</li><li>getting ridiculously drunk, or</li></ul><br />or anything else that could have resulted in me not lying on the side of the road ridiculously aware of the fact I was freezing, I quietly walked off. Really just running towards my eventual fate. Right now, I'm using my computer as extra 'heating'. I have another jumper. To find out why it's wet instead of just a little dirty we'll have to ask last evening's hungover Bodey. I'm not his biggest fan. So, another night of walking because it's too cold to sleep. Last time I was in this position I learnt that my hiking pack <strong>doesn't</strong> effectively double as a sleeping bag. This time I learnt that maybe I shouldn't have (deliberately!?) left my sleeping bag and tent at home. It's not completely my fault I'm in this situation. The weather man lied to me about the night time temperature. It's mostly my fault though.<br /><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1">Before I knew it was going to be this cold I made do by setting up a hovel in a grove using my backpack as the final wind break. I was sharing it with a number of rodents that wanted to continuously run through the grass. Off in the distance was the symphonic tune of multiple of dogs howling and barking which lead to me I drifting off to sleep with the soothing thoughts of wether foxes would take on a sleeping human (the dogs didn't seem to be getting any closer). This didn't last long because it was still cooling down around me.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1">First I went through my pack, putting on the few clothes that were dirty instead of going into the washing machine the night before. This only briefly helped but then I hit the jackpot. I needed to eat and Sarah's kit-kats were in my pocket wrapped in a bag. I grumpy tore them apart hoping that there was no note because it was unlikely to get read and that would get me in trouble. And then I saw it! Pop rocks! Holy shit. It was like heaven. True, a sleeping bag or those hand warmer things might of been more useful but far more mundane. Man now I want some more. Anyway, I had to abandon the hovel to walk to feel warm. A bit further along I decided jogging on the spot is a far better idea. I'm now aware that the last town's caravan park was full so staying there wasn't an option. It's five thirty so I've almost made it through the long night. The next few hitch hiking legs are 400 km segments so this shouldn't happen again. I'm still going to make sure my clothes are dry.</div></div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's been a while! / Getting back home]]></title>
    <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/2009/09/24/its-been-while-getting-back-home/"/>
    <updated>2009-09-24T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/2009/09/24/its-been-while-getting-back-home</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
So, in honour of Moet, I thought I'd quote a some which I'm sure he hates :P But, it has been a while since I wrote in this thing so  I figure its time for an update. Today's story: Getting back home. If you'd call it home. I'm not really sure I have a place that feels like home anymore, although I am quite proud of the house I'm living in now, but then pride isn't always a good thing. Odd fact, when I used to see that tower at uni after a short trip it would feel like I was coming home. I didn't get that when I came back to Australia :'( So this blog is about getting from Japan to Australia. Now where to start??<br /><br />Hmm, so I'd moved out of my place and was staying at my mates place for a week before I left. Lots of stories there, but that's a different entry. Who the hell decides to explore the sewers when it's raining and cold just for the hell of it? Well, me, but what kind of moron would follow me?? So anyway, I kept postponing leaving because, well, because I didn't want to leave. Funny that. But eventually I couldn't postpone it, got my stuff together, that being a cardboard box and my bag, and walked to the nearest convenience store to get a marker and make my sign for hitch hiking to Tokyo. It's sitting next to me right now actually :) The girls at the store loved it, well at least that's what I took their laughing to mean :P My first couple of lifts took me a short distances around Nagoya. First lift was two girls who were... nope I can't remember any of the details. They had a story though. The next was a girl who worked in a company because she could speak English but then never got the opportunity to speak it. Then, I spent half a day waiting next to the toll way on ramp before I gave up and started walking for a few hours. Eventually a Japanese guy who had hitch hiked all through Europe gave me a lift to a store in the toll way. There I met an Aussie guy who convinced his wife to give me a lift. They were just on holidays to meet her family, and on the way her sister seemed to go into shock, we almost got pulled over by the cops and they fed me a whole heap. Just before I got out the car to meet Snave I palmed some money into his hand because I knew the wife wouldn't approve. Crazy cultural differences :P<br /><br />Hmm, that paragraph was a bit long. I'll see what I can do about that. So, I was in Tokyo? Yeah, Tokyo and meeting Snave. So, I met him, borrowed some money to pay a debt, went out for a drink and caught a plane to Australia.<br /><br />See, that was an improvement ;) When I was booking my ticket my only requirement was that it went from Japan, to Australia. I thought I'd bought a ticket from Tokyo to the Gold Coast. I was wrong. On a side note, the Japanese staff loved my pants and hair (Even the male flight attendant wanted to touch it... wait on!), the Australian staff were rude and snide-ish. Oh yeah, and I only had $30 to get to Melbourne to meet my friend and depending on how that went hitch along the Nullarbor or beg for money. I spent most of my time in the airport cheating their hotel finder to display maps from Cairns to Melbourne and take pictures of them with my phone. Oh yeah, I was in the Gold Coast. Then I chatted to some Japanese girls I'd met on the plane and quickly ascertained that I couldn't go to any of the interesting places with my $30, so I left.<br /><br />So, umm, people picked me up and drove me? Who? This is what happens when you wait so long to write. Wait, one guy worked in the mines for half a year, saved, quite his job to sit on his arse and drink and then would start again. Not a bad life. There was an old bloke with kids my age. Then a guy who took me a decent distance and we kept stopping at water holes to go for walks and shit. It would of worked better if I'd had more sleep. He dropped me off near Townsville I think. I had a cat nap till go cold and started walking. The next guy was a champ and gave me a beer. Happiest moment of my life was sitting on that street verge drinking that beer. Then, after getting abused for bogans who mistook me for 'some cunt who should go the fuck home', wait that could be me, I was picked up by three African girls who took me back to their parents house where they told them I was a friend from uni and I helped cook and entertain the kids. They also offered for me to got to a party with them and then give me a place to crash. I hadn't had a shower for a few days and wanted to try to get a lift with a trucky so I said no. I slept on the side of the high way with no blanket or tent freezing for a few hours. Then I walked until I was too tired to walk and then tried to sleep again. Rinse and repeat. I probably could of played those cards better..<br /><br />In the morning, after waking up behind the bridge I was using to hide, I got picked up by some fishermen. They didn't say too much. Next was the army guy who wanted to know if I was an emo because then "I should get the fuck out of his car". He was going to be going all the way to Brisbane but stopped halfway, probably because I was too emo for his standards. Then near some place, the single mum picked me up said I had a face that looked trustworthy and took me back to her place after her parents had left. Sometimes I feel like screaming at people "So does a serial killer!!". Still, I got a meal cooked for me, a place to sleep, a shower and got to hang with a pretty cool girl and her kid.<br /><br />The next morning she dropped me off near the supermarket where I picked up some supplies and kept on trucking. Speaking of which, there was a cool bus there that reminded me of the one we used to live in. I think the next lift was the wife who was scared of what the husband would think, but then drove me and tried to get me a lift with some truckies. It failed but I did get my final lift of the trip.<br /><br />So I was standing there with my thumb out and this guy stops and reverses. I quickly say goodbye to the lady and run up to the car and jump in. The guy who was giving me the lift wasn't saying that much, but was going all the way to Brisbane so along we go. I started with some small talk.<br /><br />"So, what do you do?"<br />"Do you want the truth?"<br />"Why not?"<br />"I'm a debt collector"<br />"Nice, so how's that go for you?"<br />"I walk in and take shit"<br />"Ah, many problems with the cops?"<br />"Nah, mostly its me that calls them."<br />"Shit hey"<br /><br />It turned out to be quite an eventful drive. He confided in me about his original intent of reversing up close to me then taking off and spraying me in rocks. Great! And then asked if I minded if he stopped for a bong break. I told him it was his car and he could do what ever the hell he liked. So, he has his bong, takes a pill and keeps driving. By this stage the small talk had run out and my sleep deprived body was having trouble staying awake. He simple hunched himself over the steering wheel and kept driving. He stopped a few more times for these breaks, one time scaring the hell out of a school bus full of kids, before he couldn't find his pills. He asked me to look for them. I did. It was probably time to find out what they were.<br /><br />"So, what are these pills"<br />"Well, I probably should have told you before. I'm Schizophrenic."<br /><br />Joy!! Well, it did explain a few things. And I did make it to Brisbane alive and in one piece. I hope he went alright in making it to see his girlfriend #3 and cleaning up his property. Hmm... I did miss that part of the story, ah well.<br /><br />So he left me at a truck stop. I was starting to question the route I'd taken. Maybe I should double check if my Aussie bank account had any money in it. Now where to find a Bankwest on the east coast. I was told there was one and it only took me two hours of solid walking to find it. I got out $100 and had a second wind. I could do this. Quitting's for... quiters? So I stood near the freeway on ramp, thumb out, hopes held &nbsp;high and... feinted. I still haven't found out why, but I'm guessing it was my diet of bread and little sleep. Still it had only been three days. I curled up around the corner and tried to get some sleep. When I woke up I decided it was time to call it a day, I needed a friend to buy my plane ticket home. And someone did. Well, to Melbourne where I hung out with Ra for a week and borrowed money off her for the plane ticket home.<br /><br />About a week later I managed to sneak into my parents house in Balingup unannounced and scare the hell out of them. That was when they found out I was home. What did they do to deserve me as a son.<br /><br />Anyway, it's good to be back and to be seeing friends I'd been missing. Now I've just got to knuckle under, get rid of this last year of uni and pay off some debts.</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
