<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Strange | Bodey Baker]]></title>
  <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/categories/strange/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-10-31T22:43:35+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Bodey Baker]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[bodey.baker@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A short trip to 京都 (Kyoto)]]></title>
    <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/2008/06/30/short-trip-to-kyoto/"/>
    <updated>2008-06-30T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/2008/06/30/short-trip-to-kyoto</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
I just came back from a trip to Kyoto. It was pretty awesome. I got to eat tofu ice-cream, cheese cake crepe, jelly Fanta and... well I'm sure there was more. Hmm, fermented soybeans, but I eat them for breakfast everyday so they don't count. Oh, I also had octopus and seaweed salad. Thats one of my favourites.<br /><div><br /></div><div>Soo, where was I? I don't really know. Alicia from Perth is in Japan so I was traveling with her. There was a problem meeting up with her, so my morning was spent trying to call her while walking around 名古屋 (Nagoya) train station. That lasted four or so hours. I was proud of my endurance. In the end she got her phone working and we met at mine. We had a feast, it was awesome.</div><div><br /></div><div>So anyway, we got to Kyoto around ten P.M. on Saturday night and found a nice little hotel. We wandered around that night and the next morning and got some good shots (that I still can't upload). I'll put them up when I can and make some comments about them. I left for home eight P.M. Sunday night so I paid ~$100AUD in transport for less then 24 hours. Still I had a great time :)</div></div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
