<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Food | Bodey Baker]]></title>
  <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/categories/food/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-10-31T22:39:31+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Bodey Baker]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[bodey.baker@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watermelon!!!!, Japanese shoes, shopping and the war on fruit flies... well now cockroaches too.]]></title>
    <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/2008/07/07/watermelon-japanese-shoes-and-shopping/"/>
    <updated>2008-07-07T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/2008/07/07/watermelon-japanese-shoes-and-shopping</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
I chose the title to reflect my being a English teacher now. I think I should also try to palm off the last sentence as... so... I just ate marked down watermelon from the 99円 (~$1AUD) store. It was awesome even if it was shriveled and marked down. But the whole point of going to the store where I ended up buying the über cool watermelon was to get supplies for the war on fruit flies. Those of you that knew good old 57 Leura st. would know of the war on cockroaches.. we won the odd battle but we definitely lost the war. Well, over here I'm losing my battle against the fruit fries and the cockroaches are their new found allies. It turns out that not cleaning your house for over a week during summer and leaving the food stacked on your super small table is actually bad. On a sperate note, its hot over here. And not just a little hot. Where talking&nbsp;thermos hot.&nbsp;Well thats not really true, its pretty hot and incredibly humid. We're talking up to 30℃ with up to 80% humidity, presumably not at the same time, but I couldn't get pretty graph in my quick google search, just those two numbers... Oh yeah, so I have an über cool airconditioner. Well it might be über cool, I'm not really sure since I cant find the remote. Presumably it was here when I moved in and I've lost it... but you never can be too sure. What else did the title talk about? Oh yeah, it was shopping and shoes. There are lots of sales on at the moment and I still don't have too many clothes so I thought I would check them out. Shopping is <span style="font-weight: bold;">HARD</span>. Everything I found something that I liked, it was expensive and it took <span style="font-weight: bold;">so</span> long to find things I like :( I saw this awsome Gumby shirt and in the shirt Gumby was wearing an awesome shirt, but it was like <a href="http://www.google.com/search?q=88,000+JPY+in+AUD">88,000円</a>... hmm... maybe that is one too many zeros, still it was expensive. I also found a cool shirt with these gangster chickens, but I'm not so sure its worth me spending my hard earned 円 on a shirt just because there are gangster chickens on it. Oh, but I did find some cool shoes. I found these ones that are just like socks but with a sole, they're <span style="font-weight: bold;">AWESOME</span>! Apparently there made for water sports or something but I'm just going to wear them everywhere. I'm also falling inlove with the shoes that look like shoes when your wearing pants but really are just slippers. I've found out that you can go jogging in them, so maybe I will just wear them everywhere instead. Well, that was probably a boring post but I thought I should write something.<br /><br />I'll leave splitting the post into well structured paragraphs as an exercise for my readers...</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A short trip to 京都 (Kyoto)]]></title>
    <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/2008/06/30/short-trip-to-kyoto/"/>
    <updated>2008-06-30T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/2008/06/30/short-trip-to-kyoto</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
I just came back from a trip to Kyoto. It was pretty awesome. I got to eat tofu ice-cream, cheese cake crepe, jelly Fanta and... well I'm sure there was more. Hmm, fermented soybeans, but I eat them for breakfast everyday so they don't count. Oh, I also had octopus and seaweed salad. Thats one of my favourites.<br /><div><br /></div><div>Soo, where was I? I don't really know. Alicia from Perth is in Japan so I was traveling with her. There was a problem meeting up with her, so my morning was spent trying to call her while walking around 名古屋 (Nagoya) train station. That lasted four or so hours. I was proud of my endurance. In the end she got her phone working and we met at mine. We had a feast, it was awesome.</div><div><br /></div><div>So anyway, we got to Kyoto around ten P.M. on Saturday night and found a nice little hotel. We wandered around that night and the next morning and got some good shots (that I still can't upload). I'll put them up when I can and make some comments about them. I left for home eight P.M. Sunday night so I paid ~$100AUD in transport for less then 24 hours. Still I had a great time :)</div></div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
