<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Languages | Bodey Baker]]></title>
  <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/categories/languages/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-10-31T22:39:31+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Bodey Baker]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[bodey.baker@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intuitive Japanese and a SuuPaa (スーパー)]]></title>
    <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/2008/07/22/intuitive-japanese-and-suupaa/"/>
    <updated>2008-07-22T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/2008/07/22/intuitive-japanese-and-suupaa</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
Ouch. I don't know how much sleep I'd had when I wrote this, but it was pretty horrible. Anyway, I think this is the time I was wandering around my local supermarket and I bumped into someone behind me and swiftly said sorry in Japanese. I was pretty proud because up until then I had to think about things like that. Sadly.. it was a foreigner and I'm not sure they spoke Japanese. This seemed to break my swing, because I later stumbled into a poor Japanese girl (yeah, I hadn't had a lot of sleep) and said sorry in English. The small victories, hey? Anyway, back to the original:<br /><br />This actually happened pretty quick. It was about two weeks before "はい" became reactionary. I was trying to sort out some bank things with my bank in Australia (and that was an effort) and ended up saying はい to the BankWest girl on the phone. Then wondering if she understood, which was quickly followed by 'what is she thinking? Does she just think I'm some 'tard!? Wait she's moving on! Dammit &gt;&lt; I stopped listening. Whats she saying now? Ooh.. she wants me to say something.." and if that fiction is anything like what actually happened then that could explain why that bank transfer went astry stranding me in おおさか but then, me not knowing how acurate it is would also explain the problems...</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Going back...]]></title>
    <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/2008/06/30/going-back/"/>
    <updated>2008-06-30T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/2008/06/30/going-back</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
So, I'm writing this after a bit of a misunderstanding with one of my coworkers. Anyway, I've been paid to sit in a desk for eight hours today while someone was unimpressed with me so I wasn't in a good mood. And I thought a bit.<br /><div><br /></div><div>I began to think about how little I want to go back to Perth. I'm not saying that I want to stay here or that Japan/(Japanese people) are better or anything stupid like that. What I am saying is that when I go back I expect I will hate a lot of the conversations I have when I get back. I think a lot of people are going to ask a lot of stupid badly thought out questions like:</div><div><br /></div><div><ul><li>"I've heard that some Japanese writing can be read lots of different ways. That must be really hard."</li></ul>At this point I can only hope that there is a Japanese/Kanji/Linguistics/Psychology/(Computer Science) textbook handy to beat them over the head with until they physically can't ask any more questions. On a related note, I'm surprised by the number of Japanese people that tell me that lots of Kanji don't have a meaning. Luckily I can just pretend that its a translation error and they mean that lots of Kanji don't form a word on their own, or that simply because they have mostly learnt Kanji intuitively from words it is difficult to notice the common concept a given Kanji holds. Or I could be wrong and lots of Kanji really don't map to one rough concept. I hope not because its a pretty refreshing idea for me. Actually, I think that translational difficulties are one of the reasons me an Rie stayed together as long as we did. It was a convenient excuse to have more tolerance and work on problems.. sometimes :P<br /><ul><li>"Japanese people are really quiet and polite, you can be pretty loud, how was that for you?"</li></ul><div>To this I just want to beat them over the head saying "people are people, get the fuck over the Japan thing". Can you tell I've spent some time with some expats who I don't understand why they haven't gone home... wait I have heard. Money or something.. I really don't understand. My god I tried hard to avoid expats so that this didn't happen. I didn't come to Japan to hang out with a whities, much less whities who bitch about yellowies. </div><div><br /></div><div>Hmm.. I think thats it. I guess I just needed to vent a little.</div></div></div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
