<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Idiot | Bodey Baker]]></title>
  <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/categories/idiot/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-10-31T22:43:35+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Bodey Baker]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[bodey.baker@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Day 1: A good start]]></title>
    <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/2012/07/09/day-1-good-start/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-09T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/2012/07/09/day-1-good-start</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
<br /><div class="p1"><table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="float: right; text-align: right;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-oRFHH0ij6Pg/Si45Oz00twI/AAAAAAAABFY/TLZVxmIeJWM/s1600/n591195959_303442_195.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" height="320" src="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-oRFHH0ij6Pg/Si45Oz00twI/AAAAAAAABFY/TLZVxmIeJWM/s320/n591195959_303442_195.jpg" width="240" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">Me at the Gravity Center for the Magic 8-Ball trip.</td></tr></tbody></table>Ah! It's good to be moving. I woke up at some ungodly hour to do my tax and pack. Then Esu, Dougy and I drove to T's before heading to my hitching point near Muchea. It took very little time for my first lift to pick me up.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1">He was a guy from south England somewhere and was going to the gravity centre in Gingin. He'd been to most of the tourist sites in Perth and couldn't wait for the two years until his contract was up fast enough. He dropped me in Gingin and we bonded over how things closed too early in Perth and that the living wasn't dense enough. The standard stuff.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1">The next guy was a year younger than me (although he thought I was younger). He had a bunch of tattoos (some of which he'd done), built custom bikes (the reason he'd been in Perth), worked as a DJ, had done some work in security and was now working in the airport. He'd also travelled a surprising amount of Australia. He dropped me at the Geraldton maccas (so cheap) at two pm but said he could drop me off at a backpackers. I'm now on the side of the road somewhere north of there. Grumpy is probably a word that would come to mind. I'm just glad it's not raining.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1">This currently has a startlingly similar feel to the time when I was hitch hiking, maybe in townsville, where three lovely African girls took me to their families house where I helped cook and babysit the children and they fed me. Then they tried to bring me out to a party with them and told me that it was no problem and they'd sort somewhere out for me to crash the night. I said no. I said that a truck driver might pick me up over night and take me a long distance. Sometimes I need to be beaten until I'm unconscious and then when I wake up, beaten again just to drive the point home. That was a stupid decision and this one seems no better.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1"><table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="float: left; margin-right: 1em; text-align: left;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-TaS_a0-NilM/T_wUHw4C0FI/AAAAAAAAEeQ/hzItLdv3bi0/s1600/IMG047.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="clear: left; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" height="240" src="http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-TaS_a0-NilM/T_wUHw4C0FI/AAAAAAAAEeQ/hzItLdv3bi0/s320/IMG047.jpg" width="320" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">If you squint, that's Lee!!</td></tr></tbody></table>Anyway, turning down that lift lead to me meeting Lee. I'd just made it to the outskirts and had a lot of people driving past pointing. It was rather futile though because I hadn't made it to the unknown intersection ahead, so I had no idea which way I'm going. Anyway, Lee was a French hitch hiker who was on my turf and was also heading to Carnarvon that night. He didn't seem to have much luck and nor did I after meeting him. I stopped hitch hiking and walked a few km's past him before sticking my thumb out again. Only to see him drive past in the longed for comfort of the passenger seat of some car. He didn't even wave! And then… a few km's further, we crossed paths again. I hadn't managed to get a lift and apparently his fell quite a bit short. I should probably point out that Lee was doing the wise thing and waiting next to the 24hr service station. I walked past him again and got a phone call from Sammy at around sunset which I stopped short since a car was stopping for me.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1"><table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="float: right; margin-left: 1em; text-align: right;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-HHX-hM4oWSI/T_wV1lvd60I/AAAAAAAAEeY/026-KdxTlGg/s1600/IMG048.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="clear: right; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" height="320" src="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-HHX-hM4oWSI/T_wV1lvd60I/AAAAAAAAEeY/026-KdxTlGg/s320/IMG048.jpg" width="240" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">The family didn't even see it!</td></tr></tbody></table>My next lift was a family that took me into Northampton. The girl, who was around my age, was telling me about how she'd briefly owed monkeys in Indonesia. They also explained that Northampton's population of 1000 was enough to support three bars. Upper, middle and Lower. Or was it First, Second and Third? Meh. They were amazingly creative names. I had a beer in the last one. I was hoping for some food but the kitchen was closed. The girl behind the bar was a gorgeous Italian girl. We talked a bit about travelling and then instead of:</div><br /><ul><li>asking about accommodation,</li><li>hitting on her, or</li><li>getting ridiculously drunk, or</li></ul><br />or anything else that could have resulted in me not lying on the side of the road ridiculously aware of the fact I was freezing, I quietly walked off. Really just running towards my eventual fate. Right now, I'm using my computer as extra 'heating'. I have another jumper. To find out why it's wet instead of just a little dirty we'll have to ask last evening's hungover Bodey. I'm not his biggest fan. So, another night of walking because it's too cold to sleep. Last time I was in this position I learnt that my hiking pack <strong>doesn't</strong> effectively double as a sleeping bag. This time I learnt that maybe I shouldn't have (deliberately!?) left my sleeping bag and tent at home. It's not completely my fault I'm in this situation. The weather man lied to me about the night time temperature. It's mostly my fault though.<br /><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1">Before I knew it was going to be this cold I made do by setting up a hovel in a grove using my backpack as the final wind break. I was sharing it with a number of rodents that wanted to continuously run through the grass. Off in the distance was the symphonic tune of multiple of dogs howling and barking which lead to me I drifting off to sleep with the soothing thoughts of wether foxes would take on a sleeping human (the dogs didn't seem to be getting any closer). This didn't last long because it was still cooling down around me.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1">First I went through my pack, putting on the few clothes that were dirty instead of going into the washing machine the night before. This only briefly helped but then I hit the jackpot. I needed to eat and Sarah's kit-kats were in my pocket wrapped in a bag. I grumpy tore them apart hoping that there was no note because it was unlikely to get read and that would get me in trouble. And then I saw it! Pop rocks! Holy shit. It was like heaven. True, a sleeping bag or those hand warmer things might of been more useful but far more mundane. Man now I want some more. Anyway, I had to abandon the hovel to walk to feel warm. A bit further along I decided jogging on the spot is a far better idea. I'm now aware that the last town's caravan park was full so staying there wasn't an option. It's five thirty so I've almost made it through the long night. The next few hitch hiking legs are 400 km segments so this shouldn't happen again. I'm still going to make sure my clothes are dry.</div></div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deciding to go walking without a sleeping bag for one maybe two days]]></title>
    <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/2008/04/27/ill-thought-out-hiking-in-japan/"/>
    <updated>2008-04-27T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/2008/04/27/ill-thought-out-hiking-in-japan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
The date of this post is about when I started walking but the idea really started off a few days before in <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nagoya">Nagoya</a>. I had not yet done much travelling of Japan and was about to start a contract job for a webpage. I really didn't want to settle down yet so I decided I should travel before starting work. The only problem... I only had about ¥20,000 which is roughly $200AUD or currently:<br /><div><br /></div><div><br /><br /><iframe height="150" src="http://finance.google.com/finance/converter?a=20000&amp;from=JPY&amp;to=AUD" width="400"></iframe><br /><br /></div><div><br /></div><div>By the time I'd left Nagoya I had far closer to ¥14,000. I got to <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nara">Nara</a> late at night wondering if I would get to the Youth Hostel before curfew and if they would give me a room. Luckily they did and I soon ended up naked in the bath and chatting casually about where we came from and the decisions in our lives that led us here.</div><div><br /></div><div>The next day was spent looking through Nara's amazing temples (so long as I didn't have to pay) and meeting some cool guys. That not the topic of this post though so I'll put that somewhere else. That night I worked out where I wanted to go.</div><div><br /></div><div>Now I hadn't been to any <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/onsen">onsen</a> yet and a little south there was a place with three different onsen that the guide book said were the best in this area. That kinda sold me. So I did a few measurements with my fingers and figured I had to walk about 30km. I know that I walked 40km one night and my brothers walked from Bridgetown to Manji one day and thats 30kms. I was carrying a big bag so that might make it two days... thats one night sleeping on the side of the road which shouldn't be a problem. So I talked to the new guy behind the counter and took some photos of his map before heading of to bed to get a good nights sleep.</div><div><br /></div><div>Now believe it or not (I choose not to) fingers are not the best measuring devices... On top of that Lonely planet guidebooks maps are really inaccurate and I was looking across two maps that had different scales and didn't match so well. Finally I was walking through mountains and not as the crow flys.</div><div><br /></div><div>So on my first day my goal rapidly became: "Just make it south, it doesn't matter where". By the time it became dusk my goal became: "Just keep moving somewhere and don't die". By the time I set up camp under a bridge the goal had simplified to "Don't Die". Its simple I like it. Anyway... it was at about this point that I was reintroduced to how much colder it is over here. At first the concrete was just a little cold so I put on both jumpers and curled up over my hiking pack. This obviously wasn't too comfortable but I made do and got about half hours kip. Then I put on more pants and shirts and took out the uncomfortable stuff from my pack and tried again. Then I moved up to the tiny slot that was smaller then the capsules at the <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Capsule_hotel">capsule hotel</a> (actually it was about the right size for what I would want to pay for) and once again tried to sleep. Finally I resorted to using my pack as a sleeping bag. Turns out I'm small but not that small. It was at this point that I hit gold. Walk during the night and sleep during the day.<br /><br /><br /><br /><br />Some Highlights of my 4 day hike (Others hidden in the map):<br /><ul><br /><li>Meeting many police officers who wanted to know wtf I was doing and wouldn't let me sleep. Once I whipped out my laptop and double clicked on my last way point, the eyecandy seemed to convince them that I was well organised enough. I did lie to each of them about owning a tent and a sleeping bag though. And before the eye candy they would want me to keep walking and I would not have slept the night before and be staggering with a massive gapping drop that some might call a gorge off to one side..</li><br /><li>Being amazing surprised at how little water I had drunk over the last two days and how great I felt only to hardly be able to move the next evening when I woke up and got out of my drain. See, by this stage I had learnt that hiding from the friendly police was the best policy to avoid the sleeplessness they could cause and hence avoid stumbling half awake and falling to a rather adrenaline pumping death. Anyway, turns out I need to drink the same amount of water.</li><br /><li>That the smallest country towns actually do have about eight vending machines so that when you wake up and can hardly move due to your dehydration you just walk on for a few km's and hit up the nearest vending machine.</li><br /><li>Seeing some amazing scenery. Will upload pics soon.</li><br /><li>People in country towns actually saying hello in the streets, smiling and giving me food.</li><br /><li>Finally making it, asking for directions only to have the old block walk 3kms to ask the local Baker who asked his customer who asked their Mums friend. Next thing you know I have a tour guide who paid for food and entry. As if that wasn't enough they gave me a lift to the next town (<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tanabe%2C_Wakayama">Tanabe</a>).</li></ul><br />My rough path is below. Turns out that its actually about 100km as the crow flys, google keeps telling me that there are no buses there so it wont tell me the real distance :( Will update soon.<br /><br /><br /><iframe frameborder="0" height="350" marginheight="0" marginwidth="0" scrolling="no" src="http://maps.google.com/maps/ms?ie=UTF8&amp;hl=en&amp;msa=0&amp;msid=110918555514755309463.00044d13b323115dc1ee3&amp;ll=34.218204,135.772694&amp;spn=0.090492,0.061687&amp;t=h&amp;output=embed&amp;s=AARTsJp1q-x9ZkeLHrRhrd4wq0ht0vcqcg" width="425"></iframe><br /><small><a href="http://maps.google.com/maps/ms?ie=UTF8&amp;hl=en&amp;msa=0&amp;msid=110918555514755309463.00044d13b323115dc1ee3&amp;ll=34.218204,135.772694&amp;spn=0.090492,0.061687&amp;t=h&amp;source=embed" style="color: blue; text-align: left;">View Larger Map</a></small></div></div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
