<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Life | Bodey Baker]]></title>
  <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/categories/life/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-09-21T01:11:02+09:00</updated>
  <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Bodey Baker]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[bodey.baker@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attente Tourmente]]></title>
    <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/2012/07/23/attente-tourmente/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-23T00:00:00+09:00</updated>
    <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/2012/07/23/attente-tourmente</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
<br /><div class="p1"><br /><div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"><object class="BLOGGER-youtube-video" classid="clsid:D27CDB6E-AE6D-11cf-96B8-444553540000" codebase="http://download.macromedia.com/pub/shockwave/cabs/flash/swflash.cab#version=6,0,40,0" data-thumbnail-src="http://0.gvt0.com/vi/F0XrCjhI_uA/0.jpg" height="266" width="320"><param name="movie" value="http://www.youtube.com/v/F0XrCjhI_uA&fs=1&source=uds" /><param name="bgcolor" value="#FFFFFF" /><param name="allowFullScreen" value="true" /><embed width="320" height="266"  src="http://www.youtube.com/v/F0XrCjhI_uA&fs=1&source=uds" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" allowfullscreen="true"></embed></object></div><div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"><span style="font-size: x-small;">This song was one of the twenty we had in the van.</span></div><div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"><br /></div>With this group we first travelled through Coral Bay and Onslow. In the few short days it took to do this, we'd had problems with only two vans. Little did I know the mechanical workout I was going to get before this trip was over.&nbsp;&nbsp;In actual fact there was a lot of time spent on the phone to my old man or one of his friends and a lot of crash courses on different parts of the engine. Poor guys.&nbsp;We also got some soccer in, I got some rock climbing in, there was the compulsory snorkling (which I didn't do) and a fair bit of camping. I was impressed with their campfire cooking. I didn't know that&nbsp;zucchinis&nbsp;could be so delicious. And I found out that you can't use garlic and onion together. Crazy Italians. I Also learnt&nbsp;that "it's never too early for goon".&nbsp;And Me and Romain spend or first night sleeping in the 4WD so that the new couple could get some space together. I also saw bioluminescence&nbsp;in the water for my first time that I remember although I have no idea how that could be the case since I've seen it everywhere since.<br /><br /><a href="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-patNEdc3xzA/UKYAQOlpIEI/AAAAAAAAGXM/O2qxBqMSZhs/s1600/IMG068.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="clear: right; float: right; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-left: 1em;"><img border="0" height="240" src="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-patNEdc3xzA/UKYAQOlpIEI/AAAAAAAAGXM/O2qxBqMSZhs/s320/IMG068.jpg" width="320" /></a><br />On the way to&nbsp;Nanutara road house it was our turn for the van to break down. We fixed it by temporarily replacing the fuse with a bolt before limping to the road house (and later to Tom Price). When we got there, we&nbsp;randomly meeting some friends of mine who were a bit shocked to see me wandering around in the middle of nowhere without shoes or a shirt.<br /><br />Tom Price was one place I'd really been looking forward to. When we got there I spent a while running around my old hood. I checked out my old house and climbed the tree I used to climb each night as a kid after my jog around the oval. I also talked to an old mate on the phone but we couldn't arrange a meeting in the end. Then when we camped at Kings Lake, I went for a walk up the hill between there and my house looking for thunder eggs and the old caves that I used to explore. It was a lot harder to find them in the dark but I found a few. I also hoped to find some honey like we used to but no dice.<br /><br /><div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"><a href="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-iScQ5z1qUB4/UKS-rWJfM5I/AAAAAAAAGXw/bLh8Nan2C2o/s1600/IMG008.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="clear: right; float: right; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-left: 1em;"><img border="0" height="240" src="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-iScQ5z1qUB4/UKS-rWJfM5I/AAAAAAAAGXw/bLh8Nan2C2o/s320/IMG008.jpg" width="320" /></a></div>Before going to Karajini the Italian couple dropped off their van to get repaired. We could still camp together as a group. The first day was Fortescue&nbsp;falls and I learnt how to play Dixit. A game I suck at. The next day&nbsp;I even got to climb Mt. Bruce for sunrise thanks to Cedric. It meant a lot. It probably seems cheesy but my old man took me to the top of Mt. Bruce on the dawn of my 13th birthday and as the sun rose told me that now I'm a man and something poetic to do with being high up. He's always been far more poetic than I (can you tell with that&nbsp;eloquent&nbsp;description?). But it meant a lot to be able to do this again before I left. And when we left, the Italian borrowed the girls van and went to pick up theirs. We got to the meeting place and waited. And waited. And eventually found out that they had gone to fuel up at Tom Price's only fuel station only to have the car next to them catch on fire and they had to wait until the service station opened for business again.<br /><br /><a href="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-SJxh7emF_KY/UKX5oODLB5I/AAAAAAAAGXk/1TAhpoZff8k/s1600/IMG088-002.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="clear: right; float: right; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-left: 1em;"><img border="0" height="320" src="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-SJxh7emF_KY/UKX5oODLB5I/AAAAAAAAGXk/1TAhpoZff8k/s320/IMG088-002.jpg" width="240" /></a>When they caught up, me and Romain parted ways to go to Port Hedland for the night to stay with some family of mine. My uncle has backyard bar there. I&nbsp;wish I had some pics of it. It has a lot of character. The bar itself is a nice timber log places on top of a snake aquarium with a sea snake skin on the back wall and great quotes scattered around the bar in various marker pens. I got killed in pool by their children, as expected. We also watched some Aboriginal girls fishing. It was interesting watching them sitting with the VB throwing the lines in, pulling them up with a fish, taking a swig, leaving the fish to flop about and then throwing the line back in. They're far better fisherman then I.<br /><br />Between Port Hedland and Broome we stopped for a night to celebrate the Italians&nbsp;anniversary. I have a note here "I should never have explained double pluggers to them".<br /><br />We finished out time together as a group in Broome at Max and Fleur's house for a few nights. They're family friends from way back and have been having couch surfers stay with them for ages. They had some great storys and the best feature wall of any house I've seen. A <b>huge</b>&nbsp;world map. They were really warm and staying with them and their children was great. Even if the boys relished in showing me up on the trampoline. We had a good last night with as all enjoying ourselves over a few drinks. First at the beach and then at the house. Sadly, I was just really getting to know a few of the group and me and Romain would be splintering off early the next morning. He had three days to catch a flight in Darwin to see his mother so off we went. Or so we thought.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1"><a href="http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-YMDzhLQe_7g/UKS_S99I-DI/AAAAAAAAGX8/nrbfGdsQUVU/s1600/IMG017.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="clear: right; float: right; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-left: 1em;"><img border="0" height="320" src="http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-YMDzhLQe_7g/UKS_S99I-DI/AAAAAAAAGX8/nrbfGdsQUVU/s320/IMG017.jpg" width="240" /></a>The next morning saw me driving. God know's why. That was rare so I'm guessing Romain must of been pretty hungover. We made it as far as… nope we didn't even make it past the Derby turn of. The car just stopped. It was kind of hard to give more of a description than that because we were talking and listing to music but the car just seemed to loose all power and stop. Romain had no mechanical knowledge and all I wanted to do was sleep. It sucked. Slowly we had people stop and look over the car. And I harassed poor Max and my old man. They must have been getting sick of me by now. Everyone came to the same conclusion. There was no spark at the distributer. It was probably dodgy wiring or the coil. We had no tools or circuit diagram and I didn't really have the patience for someones idea of using a 12V light and some wire to test different parts of the wiring. So, we hailed cars until someone was happy to tow us to Derby. It was quite the experience since neither of us had been towed before (and Romain had recently been in a car accident with someone else at the wheel), and I didn't expect to be travelling at 110 km/hr with a tow rope this short. But, we were pretty happy as we pulled up and fate being the way it is a girl walked past and gave us her husbands number since he was a mobile mechanic. That night we splurged and had a pub counter meal before Romain decided he wanted to go fishing. I wanted to sleep so I convinced him we should push the van there. The Jetty really isn't close but we made it a fair way.<br /><br /><a href="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-WN0nBMCGCI0/UKS_q1-osKI/AAAAAAAAGYM/lV-DFPjoq_Y/s1600/IMG028.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="clear: right; float: right; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-left: 1em;"><img border="0" height="240" src="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-WN0nBMCGCI0/UKS_q1-osKI/AAAAAAAAGYM/lV-DFPjoq_Y/s320/IMG028.jpg" width="320" /></a>The next morning, fate being the way it is, the mobile mechanic messaged us just before lunch to tell us that he didn't have the time. A morning wasted. We learned a few things after we got to Derby:</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><ol class="ol1"><li class="li1">Derby isn't the best place to get repairs done. Funnily my old man did call to tell us that. It was as we were undoing the tow rope.</li><li class="li1">Small towns cook horrible seafood.</li><li class="li1">French people are horribly snobby when it comes to food. Wait… only to food?</li><li class="li1">You shouldn't tow an automatic a long way or quickly without taking out the tailshaft.</li><li class="li1">It's a long way to the wharf and probably too far to push a van that doesn't work. We made it half way though.</li></ol><div class="p1"><a href="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-R4Yt6D7ziRQ/UKTAEFe8CtI/AAAAAAAAGYQ/2wtqcJ0zPik/s1600/IMG030.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="clear: right; float: right; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-left: 1em;"><img border="0" height="320" src="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-R4Yt6D7ziRQ/UKTAEFe8CtI/AAAAAAAAGYQ/2wtqcJ0zPik/s320/IMG030.jpg" width="240" /></a>We eventually found someone who could fit us in but Romain wasn't sure he could get to Darwin in time so we decided that it might be best if he arranged a bus ticket and I drove the van to Darwin. I was also meant to renew the vehicle registration but there were a few complications with this and it looked like it was going to be simpler for me to "buy" the van off him and then "sell" it back to him. In the end we didn't and it soon became unregistered with amusing consequences. The goodbye that night was interesting because we were both in a less than perfect situations, tired and we'd known each other only ten days. The following morning the car (surprisingly) got fixed and I started driving it to Darwin, alone, but something seemed strange with the gearbox. Again, this has consequences down the line.</div></div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your pack is always full of crap and missing things you need]]></title>
    <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/2012/07/13/your-pack-is-always-full-of-crap-and/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-13T00:00:00+09:00</updated>
    <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/2012/07/13/your-pack-is-always-full-of-crap-and</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><div class='post'>
<div><div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"><br /></div><div style="text-align: center;"><object class="BLOGGER-youtube-video" classid="clsid:D27CDB6E-AE6D-11cf-96B8-444553540000" codebase="http://download.macromedia.com/pub/shockwave/cabs/flash/swflash.cab#version=6,0,40,0" data-thumbnail-src="http://1.gvt0.com/vi/cE6wxDqdOV0/0.jpg" height="266" width="320"><param name="movie" value="http://www.youtube.com/v/cE6wxDqdOV0&fs=1&source=uds" /><param name="bgcolor" value="#FFFFFF" /><param name="allowFullScreen" value="true" /><embed width="320" height="266"  src="http://www.youtube.com/v/cE6wxDqdOV0&fs=1&source=uds" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" allowfullscreen="true"></embed></object></div><div style="text-align: center;"><span style="font-size: x-small;">While I was travelling there was often music people were playing that reminds me of a time, place or people. I can&rsquo;t think of a good song for these events but this song was stuck in my head a lot just before I left.</span></div><div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"><br /></div>There&rsquo;s a bit of an overlap with this post and <a href="http://bodeystravels.blogspot.com/2012/07/day-1-good-start.html">Day 1</a> and <a href="http://bodeystravels.blogspot.com/2012/07/day-2-3-getting-to-carnarvon-and.html">Day 2 &amp; 3</a>. I hope it&rsquo;s not too much. I wrote it trying to keep myself awake one night shift on the boat.<br /><br />I&rsquo;d spent my last few nights (or weeks I believe) at Paz&rsquo;s house with Dougy and Esu. I&rsquo;d had a really great few weeks with them. Actually, I had a great time with everyone I stayed with before I left. (I may have slipped past the point that I&rsquo;d been &ldquo;homeless&rdquo; for my last year before I left Perth. Well, I was living out my car. Mostly housesitting or renting short term). I&rsquo;d convinced Paz, Dougy and Esu all to drive me north (Much to Dougy&rsquo;s chagrin since his car was on it&rsquo;s last legs) to drop me off just west of Joondalup so that I could start hitching out of Perth. Miraculously, this fine Saturday morning there was a break in the rain.<br /><br />I said goodbyes waved and watched the car leave before heading off north. I like to walk when I&rsquo;m hitch hiking. There&rsquo;s something about walking that I find relaxing. It also gives a sense of&nbsp;achieving&nbsp;something, which is a nice contrast to everyone driving past. So I walked. And walked. And doubted. It had been a while since I was hitch hiking and I&rsquo;d forgotten the golden rule. Just after you start to doubt and wonder if this was a good idea or will anyone stop, someone does and so someone did. Off I was. One of the things hitchhiking is that everyone has a story. I&rsquo;d like to list them here but they go in some other posts.<br /><br />I find that keeping up your end of the bargin (entertaining the driver) is the hardest part of hitchhiking for me. Not because it&rsquo;s hard, but because often you&rsquo;ve just woken up from the side of the road with a&nbsp; few hours sleep. And this is what happened that first night. I&rsquo;d turned down the offer of going somewhere to sleep and decided to trek on. Next thing I knew there are howling dogs, a cold breeze and no windbreak and all my clothes were wet because I&rsquo;d decided to leave instead of waiting for them to dry. Did I mention that I&rsquo;d decided last minute that the tent and sleeping back weren&rsquo;t needed and were to large to bother with in the pack? Then the only bush i could find to supplement my pack as a windbreak with was filled with rats. Well… that was day one over. And yet, being free and travelling these things weren&rsquo;t a problem.<br /><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1">The next day brought me the rest of the way to Carnavon where I&rsquo;d planned on catching up with one of the Taiwanese backpackers that had worked on the vineyard my dad manages. There hospitality was amazing I took a day off here to set up the pack (and you know, dry out the washing).<br /><br /><div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"><a href="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-G0EcHuTP94c/UKX-Brgj0wI/AAAAAAAAGWA/NWAX-KhndZg/s1600/IMG051.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="clear: right; float: right; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-left: 1em;"><img border="0" height="240" src="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-G0EcHuTP94c/UKX-Brgj0wI/AAAAAAAAGWA/NWAX-KhndZg/s320/IMG051.jpg" width="320" /></a></div>Setting out from there I made it a while before getting a lift from a&nbsp;Mauritian&nbsp;bloke going to Coral Bay. He was nice guy. We talked easily for most of the trip. He offered to take me into Coral Bay and I turned down the lift so he dropped me at the turn off and I tried to get a lift the rest of the day. No luck.<br /><br />That night I walked back to the road house to get some food and then hit the bush to find a place out of the view of oncoming traffic to get some shut eye. In Carnarvon I&rsquo;d buckled and bought a cheap sleeping bag. The next morning it was wet and I was cold. Dammit! :P After getting up I walked to the road house to get some food and it was here I saw a guy looking lost.&nbsp;I don&rsquo;t usually hang out at road houses and harass the customers&nbsp;but two days sleeping ill prepared on the side of the road was enough for me at the time.&nbsp;Then just as I was about to ask him for a lift,&nbsp;he drove off. Thankfully he didn&rsquo;t drive too far before he pulled over. I ran over to him to ask where he was going. It turned out to be Coral Bay. Great! I wanted to get to Darwin as fast as possible. There were three boat races heading north and the first was starting now. There was only a short window. I was desperate though. &ldquo;Where are you going after that?&rdquo; I asked. &ldquo;Karijini&rdquo; he said in a French accent. This was the one place I did want to see heading north (I spent a fair amount of time growing up growing up nearby and I still have quite an attachment to the place) but I didn&rsquo;t think I would have the time to spare and hitchhiking there was (I assumed) fair from simple or easy. I decided that if he was going back onto my route after this then it would be worth the delay. He was. Port Hedland and then Broome. Even better, he had a plane flight he had to catch in Darwin so we wouldn&rsquo;t be delayed too long. It was further in the future than ideal, but I would be able to see Karajini!! I exchanged names with Romain and jumped in the van. It turned out that he was travelling with four other cars. So now, including myself, nine people in total. We hung out in Coral bay for the rest of the day playing soccer and swimming. He was a decent guy and I didn&rsquo;t know it then but we were going to become good friends.</div></div></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Day 2 & 3: Getting to Carnarvon and relaxing]]></title>
    <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/2012/07/10/day-2-3-getting-to-carnarvon-and/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-10T00:00:00+09:00</updated>
    <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/2012/07/10/day-2-3-getting-to-carnarvon-and</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
<br /><div class="p1"><table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="float: right; margin-left: 1em; text-align: right;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-z4uaKPRMVTQ/T_yuJ5lrY0I/AAAAAAAAEe0/HyV9ZZLgHmY/s1600/IMG050.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="clear: right; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" height="320" src="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-z4uaKPRMVTQ/T_yuJ5lrY0I/AAAAAAAAEe0/HyV9ZZLgHmY/s320/IMG050.jpg" width="240" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">Butter with Kyle's Raphael</td></tr></tbody></table>I'm in Carnarvon and these guys are awesome. I love backpackers. Butter, her boyfriend and their friends are great. Now I just need to work out what to get them as thanks. People that say "nothing" suck&nbsp;<img goomoji="softbank_ne_jp.329" src="https://mail.google.com/mail/u/0/e/softbank_ne_jp.329" style="background-color: white; font-family: arial; font-size: small; margin: 0px 0.2ex; vertical-align: middle;" /></div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1">So, I woke up yesterday morning and wrote out the last post, then did some Korean study, packed my things that had left my bag and started walking down the road with my thumb out. It wasn't too long until someone felt sorry for me and turned their car around to pick me up. Actually, I felt sorry for them. With the amount of sleep I'd had the night before, there was no way I was going to be great company. Luckily, he loved talking so we did fairly well. I convinced him to stop at one of the road houses so that I could have a real brunch unlike the two kiddie sized chocolate bars I'd had for breakfast. Needless to say, I've spent most of today preparing. Making sure all my clothes are clean and packed, buying a cheap sleeping bad and throwing away half the crap that made it's way into my bag. Well… mostly it's just half of my first aid kit and spending the $47 in loose change I was somehow carting around.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1"><table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="float: left; text-align: left;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-tssRFqYmFYE/T_wwZWTq4UI/AAAAAAAAEeo/I9s3_cnT8fA/s1600/IMG049.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="clear: right; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" height="240" src="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-tssRFqYmFYE/T_wwZWTq4UI/AAAAAAAAEeo/I9s3_cnT8fA/s320/IMG049.jpg" width="320" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">I suck at poker</td></tr></tbody></table>I digress, back to the bloke who picked me up. He had a daughter who jumped straight in the back of the car giving me the front seat. I never know how to handle that too well but it's the norm so you just kind of mutter out a thanks. The bloke who picked me up was a Kiwi with a pet hate for the rivalry between the two countries. He educated me on a few points that I haven't bothered to check, like Farlap being from New Zealand and told me a fair bit about Carnarvon. He loved smoking, could no longer drink and had hitch hiked along the west and east coast when he was younger along with having done a bit of squatting. He'd apparently once done it with two guys who murdered someone who picked them up just for the cash in their wallets. Apparently you wouldn't of picked that they were capable of it but they were easily stupid enough to do something that…. stupid. So, after a brief stop at the cemetery, he gave me a tour of the town and dropped me off at my friends house.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1">I've now spent one night here and plan on heading off early tomorrow morning. It's raining now (my jumper was on the line outside) but should be clearing up by the morning. Wait! The rains stopped! I might try and get some stuff done in town before it starts up again!<br /><br />Oh. The plan is to stop in Dampier, Port Hedland, South Hedland, Broome and then... well I'll sort that out then. That is, presuming the plan hasn't changed by then.</div></div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Day 1: A good start]]></title>
    <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/2012/07/09/day-1-good-start/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-09T00:00:00+09:00</updated>
    <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/2012/07/09/day-1-good-start</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
<br /><div class="p1"><table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="float: right; text-align: right;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-oRFHH0ij6Pg/Si45Oz00twI/AAAAAAAABFY/TLZVxmIeJWM/s1600/n591195959_303442_195.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" height="320" src="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-oRFHH0ij6Pg/Si45Oz00twI/AAAAAAAABFY/TLZVxmIeJWM/s320/n591195959_303442_195.jpg" width="240" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">Me at the Gravity Center for the Magic 8-Ball trip.</td></tr></tbody></table>Ah! It's good to be moving. I woke up at some ungodly hour to do my tax and pack. Then Esu, Dougy and I drove to T's before heading to my hitching point near Muchea. It took very little time for my first lift to pick me up.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1">He was a guy from south England somewhere and was going to the gravity centre in Gingin. He'd been to most of the tourist sites in Perth and couldn't wait for the two years until his contract was up fast enough. He dropped me in Gingin and we bonded over how things closed too early in Perth and that the living wasn't dense enough. The standard stuff.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1">The next guy was a year younger than me (although he thought I was younger). He had a bunch of tattoos (some of which he'd done), built custom bikes (the reason he'd been in Perth), worked as a DJ, had done some work in security and was now working in the airport. He'd also travelled a surprising amount of Australia. He dropped me at the Geraldton maccas (so cheap) at two pm but said he could drop me off at a backpackers. I'm now on the side of the road somewhere north of there. Grumpy is probably a word that would come to mind. I'm just glad it's not raining.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1">This currently has a startlingly similar feel to the time when I was hitch hiking, maybe in townsville, where three lovely African girls took me to their families house where I helped cook and babysit the children and they fed me. Then they tried to bring me out to a party with them and told me that it was no problem and they'd sort somewhere out for me to crash the night. I said no. I said that a truck driver might pick me up over night and take me a long distance. Sometimes I need to be beaten until I'm unconscious and then when I wake up, beaten again just to drive the point home. That was a stupid decision and this one seems no better.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1"><table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="float: left; margin-right: 1em; text-align: left;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-TaS_a0-NilM/T_wUHw4C0FI/AAAAAAAAEeQ/hzItLdv3bi0/s1600/IMG047.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="clear: left; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" height="240" src="http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-TaS_a0-NilM/T_wUHw4C0FI/AAAAAAAAEeQ/hzItLdv3bi0/s320/IMG047.jpg" width="320" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">If you squint, that's Lee!!</td></tr></tbody></table>Anyway, turning down that lift lead to me meeting Lee. I'd just made it to the outskirts and had a lot of people driving past pointing. It was rather futile though because I hadn't made it to the unknown intersection ahead, so I had no idea which way I'm going. Anyway, Lee was a French hitch hiker who was on my turf and was also heading to Carnarvon that night. He didn't seem to have much luck and nor did I after meeting him. I stopped hitch hiking and walked a few km's past him before sticking my thumb out again. Only to see him drive past in the longed for comfort of the passenger seat of some car. He didn't even wave! And then… a few km's further, we crossed paths again. I hadn't managed to get a lift and apparently his fell quite a bit short. I should probably point out that Lee was doing the wise thing and waiting next to the 24hr service station. I walked past him again and got a phone call from Sammy at around sunset which I stopped short since a car was stopping for me.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1"><table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="float: right; margin-left: 1em; text-align: right;"><tbody><tr><td style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-HHX-hM4oWSI/T_wV1lvd60I/AAAAAAAAEeY/026-KdxTlGg/s1600/IMG048.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="clear: right; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img border="0" height="320" src="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-HHX-hM4oWSI/T_wV1lvd60I/AAAAAAAAEeY/026-KdxTlGg/s320/IMG048.jpg" width="240" /></a></td></tr><tr><td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;">The family didn't even see it!</td></tr></tbody></table>My next lift was a family that took me into Northampton. The girl, who was around my age, was telling me about how she'd briefly owed monkeys in Indonesia. They also explained that Northampton's population of 1000 was enough to support three bars. Upper, middle and Lower. Or was it First, Second and Third? Meh. They were amazingly creative names. I had a beer in the last one. I was hoping for some food but the kitchen was closed. The girl behind the bar was a gorgeous Italian girl. We talked a bit about travelling and then instead of:</div><br /><ul><li>asking about accommodation,</li><li>hitting on her, or</li><li>getting ridiculously drunk, or</li></ul><br />or anything else that could have resulted in me not lying on the side of the road ridiculously aware of the fact I was freezing, I quietly walked off. Really just running towards my eventual fate. Right now, I'm using my computer as extra 'heating'. I have another jumper. To find out why it's wet instead of just a little dirty we'll have to ask last evening's hungover Bodey. I'm not his biggest fan. So, another night of walking because it's too cold to sleep. Last time I was in this position I learnt that my hiking pack <strong>doesn't</strong> effectively double as a sleeping bag. This time I learnt that maybe I shouldn't have (deliberately!?) left my sleeping bag and tent at home. It's not completely my fault I'm in this situation. The weather man lied to me about the night time temperature. It's mostly my fault though.<br /><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1">Before I knew it was going to be this cold I made do by setting up a hovel in a grove using my backpack as the final wind break. I was sharing it with a number of rodents that wanted to continuously run through the grass. Off in the distance was the symphonic tune of multiple of dogs howling and barking which lead to me I drifting off to sleep with the soothing thoughts of wether foxes would take on a sleeping human (the dogs didn't seem to be getting any closer). This didn't last long because it was still cooling down around me.</div><div class="p2"><br /></div><div class="p1">First I went through my pack, putting on the few clothes that were dirty instead of going into the washing machine the night before. This only briefly helped but then I hit the jackpot. I needed to eat and Sarah's kit-kats were in my pocket wrapped in a bag. I grumpy tore them apart hoping that there was no note because it was unlikely to get read and that would get me in trouble. And then I saw it! Pop rocks! Holy shit. It was like heaven. True, a sleeping bag or those hand warmer things might of been more useful but far more mundane. Man now I want some more. Anyway, I had to abandon the hovel to walk to feel warm. A bit further along I decided jogging on the spot is a far better idea. I'm now aware that the last town's caravan park was full so staying there wasn't an option. It's five thirty so I've almost made it through the long night. The next few hitch hiking legs are 400 km segments so this shouldn't happen again. I'm still going to make sure my clothes are dry.</div></div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apparently more than a standard stand-up gag]]></title>
    <link href="http://porcoesphino.github.io/2012/06/29/apparently-more-than-standard-stand-up/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-29T00:00:00+09:00</updated>
    <id>http://porcoesphino.github.io/2012/06/29/apparently-more-than-standard-stand-up</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
Well, apparently wine tasting is a bit of a gimmick. Well, the paper '<a href="http://www.wine-economics.org/workingpapers/AAWE_WP16.pdf">Do More Expensive Wines Taste Better? Evidence from a Large Sample of Blind Tastings</a>' say's something like that. This is more of a note for me to flick through it later and... I figure I might want to find this someday :P</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
